John N. Rowe III papers, Inclusive: 1510-1989, undated, Bulk: 1830-1880
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Early Texas Documents, 1801-1989, undated; 2
  - Legal, 1801-1924, undated; 2
    - Legal: Ashe, John B., Eliza Ashe, Robert Mills, John W. Jockusch, 1855 June 20-21 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Legal: Atwood, Charles, Blankenlee Barnes, John Poag, 1857 April 28 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Legal: Auissan, Morris Gerard, 1855 February (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Legal: Austin, Edward T., Alfred F. James, Governor E. M. Pease, 1855 May (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Legal: Austin, Edward T., Henry Austin, and Medard Menard, 1856 February 4 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Legal: Austin, Henry, John T. Rockwood, 1857 April 27 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Legal: Austin, Henry, Samuel M. Williams and John Borden, 1852 July (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Legal: Austin, Henry, William Alexander, E. T. Austin, 1854 February 13 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Legal: Austin, H. William R. Smith, William Alexander, 1857 April (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Legal: Austin, Moses, undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Legal: Austin, Stephen. F., “Notice to Colonists to Present Themselves” (Copy), 1829 November 20 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Legal: Austin, Stephen F., Horace Chrisman, 1833 January 24 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Legal: Averitt, Phillip, James Eccles, 1847 September 14 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Legal: Ayers, David, Thomas P. Shepard, 1838 March 13 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Legal: Ayers, David, William G. Hale, 1848 June 26 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Legal: Ayres, David, J. H. Finch, 1857 June 10 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Legal: Ayres, David, J. H. Finch, Mordello S. Munson, 1857 June 19 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Legal: Ayres, David, J. H. Finch, D. E. E. Braman, 1857 June 19 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Legal: Ayers, David, C. Windran, 1857 December 1 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Legal: Ayers, Ezekiel, Carter Beamon, 1845 October 18 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Legal: Ayers, Ezekiel, Carter Beamon, 1845 October 18 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Legal: Ayers, Ezekiel, Carter Beamon, 1848 August 13 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Legal: Bachelder, L. C., [illegible] Hunt, 1845 October 15 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Legal: Bade, G. F., 1859 November (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Legal: Bade, William F., 1859 November (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Legal: Bade, William, 1859 October, November, 1858 October, November (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Legal: Bade, William F., 1859 October (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Legal: Bailey, A. J. and R. Leuther, 1854 October (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Legal: Bailey, Alphonso P., Robert Mills, John N. Jockusch, 1855 April 24 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Legal: Bailey, Isaac, Jerome M. Murphy, 1846 June 6 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Legal: Bailey, J. B., Charles Holmstrom, William Bryan, John P. Davie, 1846 December (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Legal: Baker, D. Davis D., S. Rhoads Fisher, James H. Selkirk, D. c. Mosby, John Duncan, Thomas Harvey “Agreement to Verify Mutual Claims to same Piece of Land’, 1839 February 21 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Legal: Baker, Finetta M., T. L. Williams, E. A. Kellogg, 1869 December 18 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Legal: Baker, T. H., M. A. Baker, 1889 January 1 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Legal: Ball, Albert, Israel G. Hasbrook, 1846 July 8 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Legal: Ball, Albert, Simon L. Lewis, Henry Hubbell, Lucy Johnson, 1851 July 8 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Legal: Ball, George, Samuel H. Butterworth & Wife, John H. Bennett and E. P. Hunt, 1850 April (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Legal: Ball, William B., 1838 July 21 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Legal: Ballowe, Samuel L. S., Aaron N. Hart, Ammon Underwood, Columbus R. Patton, E. L. Barstow, A. L. Morris, Henry F. Hanson, George Williams, 1856 December 26 (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - Legal: Bammaline, C. F., 1852 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - Legal: Banard, Edward L., H. Banard, Joseph A. Perkins, John Delesdenier, 1847 May 20 (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - Legal: Barnard, Henretta T., 1852 August (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - Legal: Barker, Emily, Isabella Hagadon, 1855 December 20 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - Legal: Barr, John O. and Nancy L. Hodges (Nancy L. O. Barr), undated (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - Legal: Basset, Orlando, John Nowland, William Maynard “Agreement to Deliver Goods”, 1839 April 4 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - Legal: Bates, E., N. S. Hill, Jacob Sasse, 1849 November 10 (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - Legal: Bates, Henry, John W. Butterfield, Overland Mail Company, 1859 May 17 (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - Legal: Bates, Joseph, Thomas J. Lewis, Benjamin Burris, 1850 February 9 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - Legal: Bates, Thomas, Thomas F. McKinney, William Nicholas, M. J. Keough, D. S. Kelsey, George F. Lawrence, 1840 August 6 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - Legal: Bates, Thomas B., John Clark, 1842 August 17 (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - Legal: Beamon, Carter, Stephen W. Tichenor, 1847 May 10 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Legal: Beamon, Carter, S. W. Tichenor, 1848 May 26 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Legal: Beauchamp, A. H., 1841 August (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Legal: Beaumont, Jacob K., William F. Wilson, Thomas M. Thompson, 1838 July 29 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Legal: Beaumont, Jacob K., C. L. Lewis, John Derick, 1838 December 21 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Legal: Beers, Jonathan L., Robert W. Smith, (Beers & Smith) John L. Rhea, 1846 November 25 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Legal: Beers & Smith, John S. Rhea, 1848 June 9 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Legal: Beers & Smith, John S. Rhea, 1848 June 26 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Legal: Beers & Smith, John L. Rhea, 1848 November 30 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Legal: Beers & Smith, John L. Rhea, 1848 November—1851 February (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Legal: Beers & Smith, John S. Rhea, 1849 February 24 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Legal: Behrman, George A., undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Legal: Beisner, Charles L., Eleazer P. Hunt, 1853 December 13 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Legal: Belden, Frances Emmeline (Mrs. John), DeCordova & Davison, Pizarro Edmonds, 1844 October 21 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Legal: Bell, James Ralph, 1921 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Legal: Bell, Peter H., Lawrence P. Lindley, Joseph Waterman, Michael B. Menard, Lent M. Hitchcock, 1853 November 15 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Legal: Bencroft, Jethro, Edward Burleson, 1835 September 27 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Legal: Benedict, Jared W., Stephen Southwick, Thomas B. Lewis, John S. Jones, Estate of Thomas W. Murray, 1845 December 29 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Legal: Benedict, Jared W., Thomas M. Joseph, Cephas B. Adams, 1852 January 1 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Legal: Bennett, J. H., N. A. Ware, 1853 July 17 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Legal: Bennett, Ezra B., 1855 June 8 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Legal: Bennett, John H., Estate of Edmund Andrews, 1848 May 26 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Legal: Bennett, John H. and Christian Dickman, 1849 December (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Legal: Bennett, John H., John H. and Malvinia Cecile Illies, 1850 May (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Legal: Bennett, John H., Albert Ball, 1856 June 5 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Legal: Bennett, Henry, Charles Rossingal, Wilber Cherry, Powell R. Edwards, Hamilton Stewart, 1855 November 26 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Legal: Berry, David, 1849 August, October (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Legal: Berry, David, A. A. Gardinier, James P. Hudson, 1844 December 30 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Legal: Berry, David, 1851 August (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Legal: Berry, David, Jane Hall (Harrell), 1845 October 9 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Legal: Bigmire, Henry and Dansard & Company, 1854 April (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Legal: Black, Cyrus B., Charles Black and Lilah Barber, undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Legal: Black, J. E., William Hendley, Joseph J. Hendley, John P. Sleight, 1854 April 8 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Legal: Block, Ware & Company, M. H. Bryan, 1859 December 13 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Legal: Bloodsaw, B., Appleton Gay, James W. Parker, 1840 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Legal: Boatwright, William, 1838 January (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Legal: Boltan, [Illegible], 1877 May (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Legal: Boltan, Charles L., 1874, 1875, 1876 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Legal: Bolton, John T., James N. Bolton, 1877 November 27 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Legal: Bond, Alexander, Sarah Ann Kelton, Amasa Turner, 1840 October 30 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Legal: Boothe, William A.—enlistment paper, Texas Army, 1837 January 24 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Legal: Borden, Gail Jr., Fenton M. Gibson, Estate of John James, 1838 September 14 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Legal: Borden, Gail, P. P. Borden, Wesley Coale, John Thorton, G. W. Pleasants, Piere Blanchett “Bonding Agreement for Land Purchased at Auction”, 1840 March 3 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Legal: Borden, Gail Jr., Galin Hodges, 1842 October 17 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Legal: Borden, Gail Jr. and Henry M. Smyth, 1845 January (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Legal: Borden, Gail Jr., John P. Borden, John B. Jones, Estate of Peter W. Grayson, 1846 February 3 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Legal: Borden, Gail Jr., Azuba E. Borden, John Borden, John Bissell, 1851 December 2 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Legal: Bostick, Levy, King & Park, 1801 March (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Legal: Bostick, Levi, undated (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Legal: Bowen, Ella, 1897 February 2 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Legal: Box, John, 1846 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Legal: Box, John, 1846 November 18 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Legal: Box, John, Levi Jones, 1847 November 26 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Legal: Boylan, James D., William F. Wilson, Thomas M. Thompson, 1838 July 31 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Legal: Bradley, Patrick, 1839 December 10 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Legal: Brams, T. L., Charles D. Grace, 1880 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Legal: Branham, James M., P. G. Sheet, William Hall, Robert Johnson, 1843 September 5 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Legal: Brinson, Enoch & Delila, William S. Chubb, 1858 January 16 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Legal: Briscoe, T. W., W. A. Hicks—Masonic broadside, 1850s (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Legal: Brock, John, R. P. Jones, undated (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Legal: Brock, John G., Richard Payne Jones, 1852 March 29, 1856 April 12 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Legal: Brock, Jonathan, Estate of Charles Lawrence, 1849 August 31 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Legal: Brock, Jonathan, Estate of Charles Lawrence, 1851 May 23 (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - Legal: Brock, Jonathan, Charles Lawrence, 1851 August 8 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Legal: Brock, Jonathan, Charles Samuel, 1851 April 30 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Legal: Brock, Jonathan, William Meguire, 1856 May 16 (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Legal: Brock, Jonathan, John Burdgess, William Meguire, 1857 December 31 (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - Legal: Brooks, Abijah, John A. Ford, J. Brown, E. O. Lynch, 1843 March 24 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Legal: Brooks, Elijah and William Hall & Company, Steamboat Edward Burleson, 1842 August 17 (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - Legal: Brotherton, Robert, Able Beason, Leander Beason, 1837 February 28 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Legal: Brown, George William, William B. Perry, Joseph G. Bale, G. U. Gardner, Basil G. James, 1844 November 6 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Legal: Brown, James M., 1859 April 21 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Legal: Brown, John H., C. Johnson, 1850 November (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Legal: Brown, John and Franklin, Francis M. Rowe, 1857 October 11 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Legal: Browne, Samuel P., 1848 February 4 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Legal: Browning, Nathan P., 1847 December (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Legal: Bruner, George C., Samuel H. Gates, Matthew Caldwell, 1838 March 6 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Legal: Bryan, Jacob, 1847 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Legal: Bryan, Jacob, 1850 July 1 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Legal: Bryan, Jacob and James W. Moore, 1849 (Spring) (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Legal: Bryan, Jacob, James W. Moore, 1850 April 18 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Legal: Bryan, Jacob, James W. Moore and Francis B. Whiting, 1850 July (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Legal: Bryan, Pryor, John W. Harris, Elisha M. Pease, C. Cleveland, Mary Cleveland, David Ayres, 1849 June 12 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Legal: Bryan, William, Edmund Andrews, John S. Jones, 1844 August (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Legal: Bryan, William, Samuel W. Oakey, 1847 May 11 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Legal: Bryan, William, Robert D. Johnson, Henry Hubbell, Samuel W. Oakley, 1847 June 29 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Legal: Bryan, William, Edward Hall, Henry B. Andrews, 1847 September 7 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Legal: Bryan, William L., Stephen Southwick and Allen Lewis, 1851 January (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Legal: Bryan, William, William L. Bryan, Stephen Southwick, Arthur T. Lynn and David Harvey, 1851 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Legal: Baifson, Onezims, William Alexander, D. D. Atchison and M. Dupas, 1846 August (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Legal: Buisson, Orezima, 1848 April 12 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Legal: Burdgess, John, William Mcguire, 1857 July 6 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Legal: Burdgess, John, William Mcguire, 1857 July 11 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Legal: Burdgess, John, William Mcguire, 1858 January 4 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Legal: Burger, Joseph, 1845 June (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Legal: Burger, Joseph P., L. M. Hitchcock, A. & G. Ball, 1844 October 16 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Legal: Burness, John H., John W. Middeton, undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Legal: Burnet, David G., Wilber & Fisk, New York, 1841 June (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Legal: Burnett, David G., A. Somerville, Barnard E. Bee, James Tarlton “Appointment of Lieutenant Colonel”, 1836 June 3 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Legal: Burris, Adaline R. and Samuel W. Burris, 1859 June (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Legal: Burris, Benjamin, 1856 April 28 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Legal: Burris, Benjamin, 1856 May and June (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Legal: Burris, Benjamin, 1856 August 25 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Legal: Burris, Benjamin, 1856 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Legal: Burris, Benjamin, John S. Jones, Sydney Sherman and Catherine Isabel Sherman, 1856 August (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Legal: Burritt, E. H., Gail Borden, Jr., 1837 October (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Legal: Burton, R. H., William L. Carter, Alexander Cowan, William Lester “Answer to a Writ of Habeas Corpus”, 1865 March 28 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Legal: Bush, John T., Phineas G. Merritt, 1841 December 16 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Legal: Butler Survey, Ingraham, Ratcliff & Ingraham, 1889 August 23 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Legal: Butler, George, J. W. McCown, 1854 June 28, 1854 June 12 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Legal: Butler, George, [Illegible] Kinney, 1855 June 5 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Legal: Butler, John, Butler’s Bridge, 1861 May 27 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Legal: Butler, Jonas, Michael B. Menard, 1850 April 3 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Legal: Butler, Jonas, Josiah Drew, John Lowery, Algernon P. Thompson, 1851 February 25 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Legal: Butterworth, Mary, 1854 June 1 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Legal: Butterworth, Samuel F., John H. Bennett, John Highland, 1848 December (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Legal: Bynum, Ann V., 1846 April 7 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Legal: Byrd, Major, Helena Byrd, Martha Byrd, 1841 September 27 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Legal: Caldwell, P., Capt. Smith, Lieut. Nelson, 1836 September 27 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Legal: Caldwell, Robbert, Levi M. Crow, 1838 December 27 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Legal: Callaway, Willis F., William Lippincato, 1854 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Legal: Caller, Stephan S., John S. Sydnor, Pizarro Edmunds and Charles Frankland & Company, 1841 May (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Legal: Campbell, John W., O. P. Helton, Fenton M. Gibson, 1836 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Legal: Campion, Dennis, John O’Brien, Peter J. Menard, 1842 February 22 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Legal: Campion, Dennis, William Edgar, Philip Dargan, 1847 June 9 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Legal: Campion, Dennis, Philip Dargan, William Edgar, 1847 July 3 (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Legal: Camran, Henry, undated (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Legal: Carothers, Robert J., Matthew Hopkins, 1846 April 6 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - Legal: Carper, William M., James Hapwood Crockett, Stuart, Durnett, & Brown (Indenture), 1857 June 1 (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - Legal: Carrington, F. C., 1924 (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - Legal: Carson, Samuel B., Jacob Snively, “Officer’s Subsistence report”, 1840 February 29 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - Legal: Carter, Richard, Robert D. Johnson, C. B. Adams, 1839 December 30 (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - Legal: Cartwright, Leonidas, A. Fitzgerald, 1886 July 5 (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - Legal: Cartwright, William, Sam Cartwright, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - Legal: Cary, Seth, Michael Cronican, 1844 May 9 (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - Legal: Castanie, Justine, 1855 May (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - Legal: Castelow, Thomas and Milton Yates, 1840 January (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - Legal: Castleman, Sylvanus, John Austin, El Baron de Bastrop, 1824 July 5 (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - Legal: Catenhead, Lewis P., Andrew Caddel, 1848 June 27 (Box 13, Folder 70)
    - Legal: Catlin, J. H., S. Crosby, Shaw, W. Stedman, N. G. Shelly, T. J. Chambers, P. Murral, S. H. Darden, F. L. Stockdale, A. M. Gentry, P. W. Kethell, E. D. Towns, C. C. Herbert, T. Howard, “Election Returns”, 1863 August (Box 13, Folder 71)
    - Legal: Cator, J. H., 1895 January 8 (Box 13, Folder 72)
    - Legal: Cator, J. W., 1912 March 29 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Legal: Chambodut, L. C. M., 1859 August 29 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Legal: Chaplin, John V., John C. Habermehl, 1858 August 31 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Legal: Chasco, Jose P., 1886 October (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Legal: Chaudler, A. J. and R. A. Dunkin, 1872 October (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Legal: Cherry, Wilbert, 1866 June 13 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Legal: Cherry, Wilbur and Catherine French, Isaac J. Henderson, 1847 August 7 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Legal: Chin, Robert Holmes, Albert Ball, George Ball, 1842 July 14 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Legal: Chinn, Robert H., Galveston City Company, 1841 February 20 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Legal: Chinn, R. H., Matthew B. Williamson, 1846 October 17 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Legal: Christian, Jason, 1869 March (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Legal: Chubb, Thomas, Lucy Johnson, 1851 June 4 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Legal: Chubb, Thomas, Henry B. Andrews, J. C. Mayes, Lucy Johnson, Hugh McLeod, 1851 August 7 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Legal: Chubb, Thomas and John Chubb, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Legal: Clapp, Sarah F. and Bennett Polake, Senior, 1881 April (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Legal: Clark, John vs Brig Venu, William Bourk, 1840 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Legal: Clark, John, Brig Venu, Judge Thomas, 1842 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Legal: Clark, William and Hoffman, 1858 May (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Legal: Clay, T., R. W. McCreery, 1849 February (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Legal: Cleveland, Charles S., Lucy Johnson, Thomas Chubb, 1838 May 20 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Legal: Cleveland Jesse A. H., John C. Taylor, 1852 January 5 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Legal: Cleveland, Mary D., Jesse A. H. Cleveland, 1849 Fall Term (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Legal: Clevenger, George, H. C. Hancock, 1872 July 8 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Legal: Cobb, H. A. and Pauline Eugene Marion (Marriage License), 1840 May 12 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Legal: Cobb, H. A., Elizabeth Marion, 1841 May 1 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Legal: Cobbs, Henry A., Lewis W. Dake, 1848 January 1 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Legal: Cobb, Henry A., Willard Richardson, 1848 June 7 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Legal: Cobb, H. A., James H. Spilman, H. de St. Cyr, 1850 April 25 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Legal: Cobb, Henry, A., A. J. Yates, William Perkins, 1850 June 4 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Legal: Cobb, Henry A., James C. Shaw, John H. Bennett, 1850 August 16 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Legal: Cochrane, James, 1859 November (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Legal: Cocke, James H., Edward P. Calkin, Samuel Jones, 1847 January 6 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Legal: Cocke, James H., Edwin P. Calkin, 1847 January 25 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Legal: Cockrane, W. W., William & Emeline Day, 1860 October 23 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Legal: Cody, Abner J., Don S. Stone, 1841 January 1 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Legal: Cody, Abner J., Fredrick Hilberg, 1841 June 8 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Legal: Cole, Eris, 1867 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Legal: Cole, James P., J. C. Shaw, M. Maynard, 1848 June 24 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Legal: Cole, Mason, John Cole, 1838 August 27 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Legal: Collett, John, 1837 August 26 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Legal: Collins, James P., John S. Jones, 1844 August 12 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Legal: Collins, James P., Alfred F. James, Samuel M. Williams & Henry Jenkins, 1857 December 15 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Legal: Colson, John L., Henry Rape, 1861 February 18 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Legal: Colton, William, 1849 September (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Legal: Colton, William, 1844 September (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Legal: Colton, William, Hyde A. C. and James W. Moore, 1844 December (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Legal: Colton, William and John S. Syndor, 1848 October (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Legal: Colton, William, John S. Sydnor, 1849 June 30 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Legal: Colton, William and John S. Sydnor, 1849 June (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Legal: Conrad, James M., Samuel J. Durnett, John Henry Brown, H. Stuart, 1855 May 19 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Legal: Conroy, Peter, 1847 December, 1849 October (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Legal: Norman Woods, Henry Brazil, Nicholas W. Eastland, 1842 January 31 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Legal: Cooper, William and Henry W. Patrick, undated (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Legal: Corbin, Albert G. & Mary E., David Collins, 1843 December 1 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Legal: Corbin, James C. and J. B. Bailey, 1847 July (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Legal: Corbin, J. C., 1848 February (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Legal: Corbin, James C., 1848 January (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Legal: J. and John Sorell, 1840 April (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - Legal: Couch, G. R., Martin Duvall-Survey, 1909 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - Legal: County Notice, Unidentified-poor can procure fresh meat, undated (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - Legal: Crawford, A. C., G. M. Carson, 1857 September 9 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - Legal: Crawford, C. and L. Saud, P. [illegible], undated (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - Legal: Crawford, Jane (Alias Jane Hayden), Robert Crawford, 1843 December (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - Legal: Crawford, Robert and Sam Crawford, 1841 December (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - Legal: Crist, Jacob, John M. Goens, 1863 July 25 (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - Legal: Criswell, John Y., Leroy V. Criswell, 1840 September 9 (Box 14, Folder 66)
    - Legal: Criswell, John Y., Leroy V. Criswell, 1847 March 31 (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - Legal: Cronican, James, Henry B. Andrews, William M. Sargeant, John Cronican, Michael Levitoe, Charles L. Beisner, Christopher Fox, 1850 August 30 (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - Legal: Cronican, James, John Cornican, Christopher Fox, William M. Sergeant, Henry B. Andrews, Thomas M. Joseph, 1852 September 3 (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - Legal: Cronican, John, James Cronican, 1852 July 15 (Box 14, Folder 70)
    - Legal: Cropman, A. L., Alexander Johnson, 1840 November 14 (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - Legal: Crosby, Joseph J. and McCreary, undated (Box 14, Folder 72)
    - Legal: Crothers, John, Oscar Farish, 1843 December 1 (Box 14, Folder 73)
    - Legal: Crothers, John, Charles Daniels, William J. Gourlay, John S. Jones, 1844 November 22 (Box 14, Folder 74)
    - Legal: Crow, Johanna, Bernard Crow, William Brown, 1852 February 3 (Box 14, Folder 75)
    - Legal: Crowe, William F., 1859 February 24 (Box 14, Folder 76)
    - Legal: Cruger and Moore, Brown and Brower, 1848 April 1 (Box 14, Folder 77)